A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Vice Presidential, Series 6 FA459
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Vice Presidential, Series 6
1973-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
United States. Office of the Vice President
FA459
19.2 Cubic Feet 18 volumes and 14 storage cartons.
Other Finding Aids
For other Nelson A. Rockefeller photographic holdings, please see the following finding aids:
FA454 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Nelson A. Rockefeller family, Series 1008
FA455 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Room 5600, Rockefeller family office, Series 2
FA456 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3
FA457 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 4
FA458 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, Robert A. (Bob) Wands, Series 5
FA460 Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Unprocessed photographs, Series 7
Arrangement note
The Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs are arranged in the following series:
Series 1008: Nelson A. Rockefeller family. Series 2: Room 5600, Rockefeller family office. Series 3: Gubernatorial Press Office. Series 4: Gubernatorial Press Office. Series 5: Gubernatorial, Robert A. (Bob) Wands. Series 6: Vice Presidential. Series 7: Unprocessed photographs.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement note
Rockefeller family photographic holdings are arranged into the following series:
Rockefeller family and Avery family photographs, Series 1001. William Avery Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1002. John D. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1003. William Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1004. John D. Rockefeller Jr. family photographs, Series 1005. Pocantico Hills photographs, Series 1006. John D. Rockefeller 3rd family photographs, Series 1007. Nelson A. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1008. Laurance S. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1009. David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010.
Other Finding Aids note
For other Rockefeller family photographic holdings, please see the following finding aids:
FA445 Rockefeller family and Avery family photographs, Series 1001
FA446 William Avery Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1002
FA447 John D. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1003
FA448 William Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1004
FA449 John D. Rockefeller Jr. family photographs, Series 1005
FA450 Pocantico Hills photographs, Series 1006
FA451 John D. Rockefeller 3rd family photographs, Series 1007
FA452 Laurance S. Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1009
FA453 David Rockefeller family photographs, Series 1010
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: photographs.
New York (State); New York (N.Y.); Rockefeller family -- Art collections; Political campaigns -- United States; State governments -- United States; Arts; Art, Modern; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1966; Photographs
- Vice Presidential, 6
  Arrangement
  Each contact sheet and corresponding negative has been assigned an alphanumeric number G0001-G0199 and G1000-G2599. The material is arranged by the alphanumeric number. Since the alphanumerics are presented in sequence, this arrangement is also chronological -- beginning in December 1973 and spanning through 1976.
  - Contact Sheets, 1973-1977; 1
    - G0001-G0049 - Gerald Ford Vice Presidential photographs, 1973 December 19 - 1974 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 1, Volume 1)
    - G0049-G0099 - Gerald Ford Vice Presidential photographs, 1974 February 22 - 1974 May 8 (Box 1, Folder 2, Volume 1)
    - G100-G199 - Gerald Ford Vice Presidential photographs, 1974 May 8 - 1974 August 6 (Box 1, Folder 3, Volume 2)
    - G140-G176 - Gerald Ford Vice Presidential photographs, 1974 August 7 - 1974 July 31 (Box 1, Folder 4, Volume 2)
    - G1002 - G1004 - Swearing-in of NAR as 41st Vice President of the U.S., 1974 December 19; Color (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1005 - Reception after swearing in, 1974 December 19; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1006 - NAR reception after swearing-in as 41st Vice President of the U.S., 1974 December 19; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1007 - Nelson Rockefeller reception after swearing-in as 41st VP of the U.S., 1974 December 19; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1008 - Stan Scott party, 1974 December 19; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1009 - VP Nelson Rockefeller begins his first day on the job, 1974 December 20; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1010 - VP NAR begins his first day on the job at the U.S. Senate, 1974 December 20; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1011 - VP NAR begins his first day on the job (Mrs. R. in some), 1974 December 20; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1013 - G1014 - GRF and NAR with economic advisers, 1974 December 21; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1015 - Arthur Burns, 1975 January 8; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1016 - G1017 - David Kennerly, 1975 January 9; Color (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1018 - Nelson A. Rockefeller portrait, 1975 January 9; Color (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1019 - Sultan of Oman, 1975 January 10; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1020 - G1022 - Anderson House - Rocky greets the Sultan of Oman, 1975 January 10; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1023 - CIA investigation committee, 1975 January 13; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1024 - VP with CIA Investigating Committee, 1975 January 13; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1025 - G1027 - CIA investigation committee, 1975 January 13; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1028 - G1029 - Rocky meets the Press, 1975 January 13; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1030 - VP Senate Office - Rocky confers with his staff. EOB - Rocky meets with John McCone and Admiral Anderson. Cabinet Room - Rocky attends the GOP Leadership Meeting, 1975 January 14; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1032 - VP Senate Office - Rocky greets the new senators, 1975 January 14; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1033 - VP Senate Office - Rocky confers with his staff, 1975 January 14; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1034 - Rocky attends a Republican leadership meeting with GRF, 1975 January 14; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1035 - VP and Mrs. Rockefeller greet new Senators, 1975 January 14; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1036 - VP and Mrs. Rockefeller, 1975 January 15; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1037 - VP Rockefeller and staff in Senate office, 1975 January 15; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1038 - Rocky swears-in the Commission to investigate the CIA, 1975 January 13; Color (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1039 - Rocky meets the Commission investigating the CIA, 1975 January 13; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1040 - Rocky and GRF meet with Governors and Mayors in the East Room to discuss the Economy, Rocky confers with his staff, 1975 January 16; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1041 - Rocky and GF meet with Governors and Mayors in the East Room to discuss the Economy, David Belin, 1975 January 16; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1042 - Untitled, 1975 January 16; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1043 - Rocky meets with the President Economic Advisors, 1975 January 16; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1044 - Rocky swears-in David Belin as Director investigating CIA, 1975 January 16; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1045 - Rocky swears-in Sol Neil Corbin as vice counsel investigating CIA, 1975 January 16; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1046 - Yigal Allon, 1975 January 17; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1047 - VP Rockefeller and staff, 1975 January 18; Color (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1048 - John D. Rockefeller, 3rd, 1975 January 21; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1049 - Rocky meets with Helms and McCone on CIA activities, Rocky meets with GRF and Buchen in the Oval Office, 1975 January 20; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 5, Volume 3)
    - G1050 - Nelson A. Rockefeller portrait, 1975 January 21; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1054 - Rocky watches GRF meet the Press on TV, Rocky appears on TV with Sen. Hugh Scott, 1975 January 21; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1055 - National presidents of vocational student organizations, 1975 January 22; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1056 - G1057 - Nuclear Regulatory Commission swearing in, 1975 January 23; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1058 - Governor Hugh Carey (NY), 1975 January 23; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1059 - Rocky chats with the Press aboard Air Force II, Rocky works on his speech aboard Air Force II, 1975 January 23; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1060 - National business leadership conference; Senator Randolph (WV), 1975 January 23; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1061 - G1062 - National business leadership conference, 1975 January 23; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1063 - Marjorie Lynch; Joint Chiefs of Staff, 1975 January 27; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1064 - Senator Jennings Randolph (WV); Marjorie Lynch, 1975 January 27; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1065 - John Marsh; William Coleman; Linwood Holton, 1975 January 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1066 - Felipe Benavides; Linwood Holton; Washington Press Club, Walter Cronkite, 1975 January 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1067 - Washington Press Club salute to Congress, 1975 January 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1068 - Felipe Benavides; Getty Conservation Prize, 1975 January 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1069 - Henry Kissinger and James Schlesinger, 1975 January 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1070 - Cabinet Meeting, 1975 January 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1071 - G1074 - New Jersey campaign trip, 1975 January 29; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1075 - Rocky campaigns for the GOP in New Jersey, Winthrop Rockefeller, 1975 January 30; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1076 - Winthrop Rockefeller, 1975 January 30; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1077 - Senators in room s-207, 1975 January 30; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1078 - Mrs. Rockefeller with Mrs. Harold Wilson, 1975 January 30; Color (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1079 - Senate luncheon with Prime Minister Wilson, 1975 January 30; Color (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1080 - Biomedical Commission swearing in, 1975 January 31; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1081 - Rocky and Scowcroft meets Israel's Foreign Minister Yigal Allon, 1975 January 18; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1082 - John McCone; Philip Buchen, 1975 January 20; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1083 - George Bush, 1975 February 3; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1084 - VP Rockefeller in his new Senate Office Building office, 1975 February 4; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1085 - Governor Carey (NY) and Mayor Beame (NYC), 1975 February 6; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1086 - Prime Minister Ali Bhutto, Pakistan, 1975 February 6; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1087 - G1088 - Attorney General Edward Levi swearing in, 1975 February 6; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1089 - Senator Hugh Scott (PA); outstanding trucker, 1975 January 20; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1092 - Jim Cannon and Dick Dunham, 1975 February 13; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1093 - Nelson A. Rockefeller tribute, New York, 1975 February 14; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1094 - GRF; Art Godfrey birthday party, 1975 February 13; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1095 - Nelson A. Rockefeller tribute, Waldorf Astoria, New York, 1975 February 14; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1097 - Nelson A. Rockefeller tribute, New York, 1975 February 14; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1098 - Whitman, Walker, Cannon and Dunham; Sol Linowitz; NAACP representatives on Rule 22, 1975 February 20; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1099 - National Affairs Association conference, 1975 February 19; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 6, Volume 3)
    - G1100 - Felipe Benavides reception, Pan Am Union, 1975 February 19; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1101 - Congressional dinner, White House, 1975 February 19; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1102 - Mayflower Hotel. Rocky speaks to the National Conference of Governors. Pan American Union Bldg. Rocky attends a reception in honor of Felipe Benavides, 1975 February 19; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1103 - Congressional dinner, White House, 1975 February 19; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1104 - Congressional dinner, White House; Vietnamese delegates, 1975 February 19; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1105 - G1106 - NAR and staff discuss rule no. 22, 1975 February 20; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1107 - G1111 - Governors' conference dinner, White House, 1975 February 20; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1112 - NAR and staff discuss rule no. 22, 1975 February 20; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1113 - Black Enterprises Business Achievement Awards, 1975 February 21; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1114 - Marsh and Cannon; Black Enterprises Achievement Awards; Rule #22 with Sens. Helms (NC), Brooke (MA), and Hansen (WY), 1975 February 21; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1115 - Cabinet Room - Rocky briefs the President and the Cabinet on the structure of the Domestic Council, U.S. Senate - Rocky gives the Black Enterprise Business Achievement?, 1975 February 21; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1116 - Black Enterprises Achievement Awards; Rule no. 22 with Sens. Helms (NC), Brooke (MA), and Hansen (WY), 1975 February 21; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1117 - Cabinet Room. Rockefeller explains to the President and the Cabinet his ideas for the structure of the Domestic Council, 1975 February 21; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1118 - NAR and staff discuss rule no. 22, 1975 February 25; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1119 - Cannon, Dunham and Simon discuss the restructuring of the Domestic Council, 1975 February 26; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1120 - U.S. Senate - Rocky discusses Rule no. 22 with his staff and Senator Brock. Treasury Dept. - Rocky, Jim Cannon, and Richard Durham are briefed by Secretary Simon on Domestic Policy, 1975 February 26; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1121 - Society of Automotive Engineers, Detroit, 1975 February 26; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1122 - G1124 - Cole on domestic policy; Society of Automotive Engineers, Detroit, 1975 February 26; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1125 - Society of Automotive Engineers, Detroit, 1975 February 26; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1126 - Arthur Fleming award winners, 1975 February 27; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1127 - Rocky meets with Flo Atherton, Norm Hurd, Dr. Carmichael and RN Chairman Mary Louise Smith, and Secretary Morton, 1975 February 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1128 - Harry Albright reception, Foxhall residence, 1975 February 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1129 - Rogers Morton; Harry Albright reception, Foxhall residence, 1975 February 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1130 - Harry Albright reception, Foxhall res., 1975 February 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1131 - Resignation from Commission on Critical Choices for Americans, 1975 February 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1132 - Reception for members of the Commission on Critical Choices for Americans, Fifth Avenue residence, 1975 February 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1133 - Resignation from Commission on Critical Choices for Americans, 1975 February 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1134 - Reception for members of the Commission on Critical Choices for Americans, Fifth Avenue residence, 1975 February 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1135 - G1136 - Resignation from Commission on Critical Choices for Americans, 1975 February 28; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1137 - Meeting with staff, Foxhall residence, 1975 March 2; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1138 - Attorney General Edward Levi, 1975 March 2; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1139 - Cannon, Dunham, and Attorney General Levi discuss domestic policy, 1975 March 2; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1140 - G1141 - National Conference on Christians and Jews, 1975 March 4; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1142 - Indonesian Vice President Hamengku Bumono, 1975 March 4; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1143 - Secretary Of Agriculture Earl Butz, 1975 March 5; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1144 - G1146 - Washington Hilton Hotel - Rocky speaks to the Republican Leadership Conference, 1975 March 7; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1147 - Secretary Of Commerce Frederick Dent, 1975 March 10; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1148 - Secretary Of Commerce Frederick Dent, 1975 March 10; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1149 - GRF; Japanese economic mission, 1975 February 12; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1150 - Alan Greenspan, 1975 March 13; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 7, Volume 4)
    - G1151 - GRF, Cabinet and rule no. 22; Sen. Kennedy (MA), 1975 March 13; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1152 - GRF, Cabinet and rule no. 22, 1975 March 13; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1153 - Milton Pitts and White House barbershop, 1975 March 17; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1154 - Veteran Administration - Rocky meets with Richard Roudebush on Domestic Policy, 1975 March 18; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1155 - VA Administrator Richard Roudebush, 1975 March 18; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1156 - Cannon and Dunham, 1975 March 18; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1157 - Coal industry representatives, 1975 March 21; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1158 - Senators Brooke (MA) and Pell (DE); Andrew Heiskell, 1975 March 21; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1159 - CIA investigation advisors, 1975 March 24; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1160 - GRF, Dunham and Cannon, 1975 March 20; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1161 - NAR meets with Henry Dorman. U.S. Senate: Rockefeller appears on TV with Senators Brooke and Pell, 1975 March 25; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1162 - Ambassador to Japan Hodgson, 1975 March 25; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1163 - G1174 - Funeral for King Faisal, Saudi Arabia, 1975 March 27; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1175 - Funeral for King Faisal, Saudi Arabia, 1975 March 27; Color (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1176 - G1178 - Funeral for King Faisal, Saudi Arabia, 1975 March 27; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1179 - G1180 - Niagara Falls, N.Y. - VP Rockefeller attends the funeral of New York Senator Earl Brydges, 1975 April 1; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1181 - G1182 - The Transportation Dept. - Rocky and his domestic advisors are briefed by Secretary Coleman on domestic transportation policy, 1975 April 2; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1183 - Commerce Dept. - Rockefeller awards the Handicapped for being outstanding Federal employees, 1975 April 3; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1184 - G1186 - The White House Grounds - Thomas and Mary Morgan tour the Oval Office and the White House with their children: Sabrina, Michael, and Geoffrey, 1975 April 5; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1187 - The White House Grounds - Thomas and Mary Morgan tour the Oval Office and the White House with their children: Sabrina, Michael, and Geoffrey, 1975 April 5; Color (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1188 - G1189 - NAR swears-in Henry P. Smith III as the U.S. Commissioner on the International Joint Commission of the U.S. and Canada, 1975 April 8; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1190 - G1193 - New Orleans, Louisiana. VP Rockefeller addresses the American Newspaper Publishers Association Luncheon, 1975 April 10; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1194 - U.S. Capitol - Joint Session of Congress. VP Rockefeller listens to President Ford's message to Congress on the State of the World, 1975 April 10; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1195 - New Orleans, Louisiana. VP Rockefeller addresses the American Newspaper Publishers Association Luncheon, 1975 April 10; Color (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1196 - The Kennedy Center. VP Rockefeller addresses the President Personnel Interchange dinner, 1975 April 10; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1197 - G1199 - U.S. Capitol - Joint Session of Congress. VP Rockefeller listens to President Ford's message to Congress on the State of the World, 1975 April 10; Black and White (Box 2, Folder 8, Volume 4)
    - G1200 - G1201 - EOB Conference Room. VP Rockefeller participates in a Governors meeting on Energy, 1975 April 10; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1202 - G1203 - The Washington Hilton Hotel. VP Rockefeller addresses the National Association of Manufacturers luncheon, 1975 April 11; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1204 - G1205 - Conference Room. VP Rockefeller meets with the White House Fellows, 1975 April 10; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1206 - G1229 - Taipei, Taiwan. VP Rockefeller and the American delegation give their condolences to Mme. Sung Mei-Ling Chiang by the passing of Pres. Chiang Kai-Shek, 1975 April 13; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)
    - G1207 - Untitled (most likely same as G1206), 1975 April 13; Black and White (Box 3, Folder 9, Volume 5)